paulcbuff.com 2017-06-06

# Paul C. Buff - Privacy Policy

Paul C. Buff, Inc.™ respects your privacy.  
Any personal information you provide to us, including your name, your physical or email address, or your telephone number, will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of Paul C. Buff, Inc.™ at any time.

Ordering Information  
Information gathered for the purpose of fulfilling a merchandise order will be used exclusively for that purpose. We will not use any of the information collected in product ordering for any purpose not directly related to the processing of your order. Your email address and other contact information will only be used outside of order processing in the event that we need to contact you to provide important information about the product(s) purchased.

External Sites  
Paul C. Buff, Inc.™ is not responsible for the content of external internet sites. While we offer links to other sites, and will always do our best to ensure that these links are valid, we are not directly affiliated with these sites, and cannot be held responsible for their content, their offers, or their respect for your privacy. You are advised to read the privacy policy and any other policies of those external sites before disclosing any personal information.

Cookies  
A "cookie" is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows the website to recognize you each time you visit this site. Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and Paul C. Buff, Inc.™ does not use cookies to collect personal information.

Remember The Risks Whenever You Use The Internet  
While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to Paul C. Buff, Inc.™ and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition, other internet sites or services that may be accessible through Paul C. Buff, Inc.™ have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions. Please contact those vendors and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies. For any other information contact us.
